module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is typically the center color in candy corn?', 
      a: 'White', 
      b: 'Yellow',
      c: 'Orange',
      d: 'Red',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Bram Stoker was famous for writing which novel?', 
      a: 'Carmilla', 
      b: 'Jekyll and Hyde',
      c: 'Frankenstein',
      d: 'Dracula',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where does the annual "Village Halloween Parade" take place?', 
      a: 'Boise ID', 
      b: 'Sleepy Hollow NY',
      c: 'Chicago IL',
      d: 'New York City',
      answer: ''
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the English word "hallow" mean?', 
      a: 'Sin', 
      b: 'Spirit',
      c: 'Saint',
      d: 'Spook',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where did Halloween originate?', 
      a: 'Rome', 
      b: 'America',
      c: 'Scotland',
      d: 'Ireland',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'In foklore, a "lycanthrope" is another name for what?', 
      a: 'Dracula', 
      b: 'Werewolf',
      c: 'Witch',
      d: 'Zombie',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the first feature length zombie film?', 
      a: 'Night of the Living Dead', 
      b: 'Day of the Dead',
      c: 'House of 1000 Corpses',
      d: 'White Zombie',
      answer: ''
    },
    {
      question: '"The Killer Clown" serial killed was also named "____ the Clown?"', 
      a: 'Eric', 
      b: 'Pogo',
      c: 'Bozo',
      d: 'Bobo',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which artist covered the song "This is Halloween" in 2006 for the The Nighmare Before Christmas\'s special edition soundtrack reissue?', 
      a: 'Fallout Boy', 
      b: 'Pantera',
      c: 'Marilyn Manson',
      d: 'Kelly Clarkson',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'The Whitechapel murders who done by who?', 
      a: 'Sweeney Todd', 
      b: 'Jack the Ripper',
      c: 'Samuel Mason',
      d: 'Charles Manson',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};